Tour Pamphlet - Profile Questionnaire
Name: Chiyoko Sonoda
What's your favorite food?
Of course, sweet chocolate!
I love all kinds of sweets, though.
Please share your enthusiasm about the tour!
I'll do my very best together with everyone
in Hokura and 283 Productions!
What kind of idol do you want
to become through this tour?
An idol who can bring smiles
to everyone, like a hero!!
An idol who can give back
to those who support us.
An idol who puts their heart
into everything.
The world's
number one
top idol,
together with
everyone
in Hokura.
- Do your best!!
- Thank you for giving me
the chance to become an idol!
An idol who can make dreams come true, together with everyone.