1st Album Release Confirmed
Featuring All Units!
First National Tour
Confirmed!
- I heard those idols who were
childhood friends are being sidelined, lol.
- Serves them right. Don't underestimate
being an idol.
- LOL
- They weren't even singing, lol.
- I wish they'd think about how the fans feel.
An album release and
nationwide tour were
announced, making it
a truly joyous and
surprising event.
Today
- Choco-chan, great job at the
Halloween event! You were so cute!
- My dear friend really is an amazing idol!!
Thank you for taking the audition in my place.
And thank you for becoming an idol.
- Asumi-chan, thank you sooo much!!
I really wanted to find you and wave at you.
- What about you, Sakuya?
- Thank you all for the wonderful ideas.
- I want to do the exact same things you all want to do.
Noctchill
Album Tracklist
Illumination Stars: Hikari no Destination (New Song)
L'Antica: Babel City Grace (New Song)
Houkago Climax Girls: Yumesaki After School (New Song)
Alstroemeria: Alstroemeria (New Song)
Straylight: Wandering Dream Chaser (New Song)
- What about you, Sakuya?
- Thank you all for the wonderful ideas.
- I want to do the exact same things you all want to do.
Today
- They say it can fly.
Noctchill
Album Tracklist
Illumination Stars: Hikari no Destination (New Song)
L'Antica: Babel City Grace (New Song)
Houkago Climax Girls: Yumesaki After School (New Song)
Alstroemeria: Alstroemeria (New Song)
Straylight: Wandering Dream Chaser (New Song)
Noctchill: We Are Always Who We Are (New Song)