Comfy Tea Time
Filming in Progress
ALSTROEMERIA Comfy Tea Time! #01
Protecting Peace on Earth
The Ultimate Force of Righteousness
Pastel Nice is coming to the Sakura Mall!
When: 4th Sunday 14:00~ Where: Special Central Stage Free
Stay vigilant! Be careful when using fire!
Justice Five
Spring Fire Prevention Campaign
Pastel Nice x Hokago Climax Girls
Special Hero Show in Sakura Mall
Where: Sakura Mall Central Plaza Special Stage
Script
Weekly Coming Up Hit!
Pastel Nice Hero Show &
Hokago Climax Girls Special Concert
Time/14:00
Hokago Climax Girls
Green Room
Hokago Climax Girls Hero Show & Concert
Operation Exciting Hero Show
Involve the children!!
Special Mission
Hokago Climax Girls
Hero Show & Concert
Yumesaki After school